<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Introductions | m._.se0k's BLOG</title><link>http://localhost:1313/en/introduction/</link><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/en/introduction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description>Introductions</description><generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><image><url>http://localhost:1313/media/icon_hu7729264130191091259.png</url><title>Introductions</title><link>http://localhost:1313/en/introduction/</link></image><item><title>⚒️SKILLS⚒️</title><link>http://localhost:1313/en/introduction/skills/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/en/introduction/skills/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="c">C++&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>With C++, I have developed a strong understanding of low-level memory management, object-oriented programming principles, and efficient algorithm design. C++ has been my go-to language for performance-critical applications, where I’ve explored advanced features like templates, STL (Standard Template Library), and multi-threading. I am comfortable working with complex data structures and algorithms, which has allowed me to build optimized solutions for real-world problems. My experience with C++ has also strengthened my problem-solving skills, making it easier to tackle challenges that require both speed and resource efficiency.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="java">JAVA&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Java, being a language known for its platform independence and scalability, has been instrumental in my journey as a developer. I have utilized Java extensively for building robust backend systems, as well as for developing desktop and web applications. Java’s rich ecosystem, including frameworks like Spring, has empowered me to create well-structured, maintainable applications that are scalable and easy to deploy. My experience spans from creating multithreaded applications to leveraging Java’s garbage collection for efficient memory management, all while adhering to best practices in object-oriented design. Java’s wide community support and extensive libraries have enabled me to quickly adapt to various challenges in software development.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>